socialvibe.com 2012-10-21

# SocialVibe

Last updated November 3, 2010 

Your privacy is important to SocialVibe (“SocialVibe” or “Service”) and, as described in this Privacy Policy, we have designed various measures to protect information about you from unauthorized disclosure to others. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and, in certain circumstances, share your Personally Identifying Information, which refers to information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate an individual or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual (i.e., physical address, email address, first and last name) (“PII”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, and if you have any questions, feel free to contact us at privacy@socialvibe.com. 

**What We Collect**

We may be able to collect information from social networking systems on which you have used Zynga Games, Facebook, or SNS Apps (in accordance with the terms of use of those systems), which would then also be covered by this Privacy Policy. 

When you use an SNS App on your social network page or use an SNS App on someone else's page, we may record information regarding the use of that SNS App, and we may collect other information, namely, PII or NPII as defined below, that is visible on your social network page in accordance with the relevant terms of use associated with that page. 

Note that since most SocialVibe Software is served through SNS Apps, it is your responsibility to read and accept their Terms of Use, their Privacy Policy prior to continuing. 

SocialVibe’s site may contain links to other websites; these links are provided solely for your convenience. Links taken to other sites are done so at your own risk and SocialVibe accepts no liability for any linked sites or their content. When you access an external website, keep in mind that SocialVibe has no control over its content. 

Any link from SocialVibe to an external website does not imply or mean that SocialVibe endorses or accepts any responsibility for the content or the use of such website. SocialVibe does not give any representation regarding the quality, safety, suitability, or reliability of any external websites or any of the content or materials contained in them. It is important for users to take necessary precautions, especially to ensure appropriate safety from viruses, worms, Trojan horses and other potentially destructive items. 

When visiting external websites, users should review those websites' privacy policies and other terms of use to learn more about what, why and how they collect and use any PII. 

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by SocialVibe. 

You should also be aware that most content delivered through SocialVibe originates with another content provider. Such other content providers may place “cookies” on your browser, or otherwise gather PII and/or NPII about you, including by asking you to provide information through the site itself. 

Finally, in order to provide the best possible service and to allow us to make certain internal reports and make recommendations, we collect aggregate information that is Non Personally Identifying Information (“NPII”) information that does not uniquely identify an individual. For example, we collect information about the use of the SocialVibe, including information about users SNS Apps on other sites, such as internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time (“Activity Information”). 

By using the Service, you consent to our retaining all the above‐described NPII information in anonymous form as long as SocialVibe sees fit. 

**Children Under the Age of 13**

SocialVibe does not knowingly collect or solicit PII from anyone under the age of 13. No one under age 13 may provide any PII to or on SocialVibe. In the event that we learn that we have collected PII from a child under age 13 we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child fewer than 13, please contact us at privacy@socialvibe.com. 

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. 

**How We Use Your Information**

We do not sell or rent your PII to any third party. We may, however, use certain information about you that is NPII. 

We collect and use NPII or publicly available information to determine the kinds of content that you would like to view and to assist any advertisers in targeting their advertising. In addition we use NPII and certain technical information about your computer and your access of the Service (including your internet protocol address) in order to operate, maintain and manage the SocialVibe. 

SocialVibe may disclose NPII information to its advertisers, agencies and network partners (hereinafter “Partners” or “Third Parties”) where SocialVibe’s engagements is offered to users in order to provide the Service, resolve service problems and correct errors in the Service, to communicate with you about the Service, to provide you with advertising and promotional information in connection with the Service, and to enhance your experience on the Service. However, we do not give our partners the right to share this information. 

Due to our contractual obligations with these Third Parties and the need to share information to deliver and support the Service, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt‐out of sharing information with these Third Parties if the PII is collected when a user explicitly enters for the purpose of providing it to one of our advertisers (i.e., entering a sweepstakes); however a user may opt out of sharing information when a user signs up with Socialvibe.com, our charity site, and provides a real first name, last name and email address. In this case, SocialVibe will permit users to close/cancel their account and SocialVibe will delete the user’s record from our database. 

SocialVibe, some Partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the content that you transmit to the Service in order to provide the Service and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

You understand and agree that we may access, preserve, and disclose any information we may have about you and the contents of your account if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to avoid liability, to comply with legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, or court order, or to protect our rights and property, or that of our affiliates or the public. SocialVibe is not required to question or contest the validity of any search warrant, subpoena or other similar governmental request that SocialVibe receives. 

**Controlling and Securing Your Personal Information**

Be advised that if you send messages or post material containing PII, that information may be collected and used by others. SocialVibe takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and security measures to guard against unauthorized access to where we store personal data. 

SocialVibe restricts access to PII to SocialVibe employees, Partners, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on SocialVibe’s behalf. These individuals or entities are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**Transfer of Information**

We reserve the right to transfer your PII in the event of a transfer of ownership of SocialVibe or the acquisition of substantially all the assets of SocialVibe related to the business which collected such information, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. If a transaction described above occurs, we will ensure the confidentiality of any PII involved in such transaction and provide notice before PII is transferred if the PII is subject to substantially different privacy policy. 

**Others' Information**

You may decide to provide us with another person's email address so that we may facilitate your communication with other people through the Service. 

You may also provide us with another person's contact information for purposes of delivering information through SNS Apps. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to receive content through an SNS App. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations from SocialVibe. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above. 

**Cookies**

The Service sends "cookies" to your computer when you access the SocialVibe, or otherwise view content through another source, such as a Zynga game, or use of an SNS App. A cookie is a small text file recorded on your hard drive that identifies you as a unique user and contains certain information about your particular login session and/or your use of the Service and the Service uses such cookies as described in here. The Service uses cookies to improve the quality of our service, make recommendations to users and or advertisers, and to make the Service easier to use for our users. 

**Use of Information**

SocialVibe may contain links to other web sites, and content in SNS Apps may be hosted by other web sites. In addition, as described above, most content offered through SocialVibe or SNS Apps is served or hosted by other sites. These other sites maintain their own policies regarding cookies and the collection and use of personal information. It is up to you to review those policies yourself. 

**Third Party Advertising Companies**

We use third‐party advertising companies on certain SNS Apps. Our system and the third‐party advertising technology use information derived from Activity Information, SocialVibe's cookies on your hard drive, your visits to our site or other sites, such as the Zynga games that you view, and the SNS Apps you use to target advertising within our Service or Zynga or SNS Apps. In addition, our advertisers may use other third‐party advertising technology to target advertising on our site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third‐party cookie or cookies may be placed on your computer. Similarly, third‐party advertising companies may provide us with pixel tags (also called “clear gifs” or “beacons”) to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Beacons enable us to recognize a browser's cookie when a browser visits the site on which the beacon is located, and to learn which links bring users to a given site. 

SocialVibe does not provide any PII to third‐party advertising companies. Note, however, that if an advertiser asks SocialVibe to show an advertisement to users with certain characteristics (for example, women ages 18‐24) or a segment of that group (for example, women ages 18‐24 who have viewed certain categories of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the third‐party advertising company may conclude that you have the characteristics of the audience that they are trying to reach. 

**California Residents: Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California law, California Residents who have an established business relationship with SocialVibe or one of its subsidiaries may choose to opt out of SocialVibe disclosure of PII to third parties for direct marketing purposes. As detailed above, our policy is not to disclose PII collected online to a third party for direct marketing purposes without your approval. If you choose to opt‐out at any time after granting approval, email privacy@socialvibe.com. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.
